cheatshero.com 2009-05-02

# CheatsHero.com

This Privacy Policy and Disclosure Statement explains in general terms how  Cheatshero.com  protects the privacy of your personal information. The principles set out in this Privacy Policy and Disclosure Statement will apply to any personal information you provide to  Cheatshero.com  via our web site or service under any agreement or arrangement and to information which we collect about you from other sources.   
This Privacy Policy does not apply to acts and practices which relates directly to the employee records of  Cheatshero.com 's current and former employees.

How we collect your personal information:   
We gather demographic information (like your city of residence and/or age). We may share some of this information with our professional advisors or consultants for our own research purposes. However the information shared will be limited to non-personally identifying demographic information shared under cover of a confidentiality agreement. If you choose to become a Paid Member, we collect financial information (like your credit card number and expiry date). We will only use this information in the course of providing our service to you. 

Use of Private information:  
The specific information we collect is shared with other organizations for marketing purposes and is not personally identifiable information. We keep the information you have given us for as long as you are a member of our service.  
You can always verify or request the deletion of the personally identifiable information we have collected and change your registration information by contacting Customer Service. Any such request may also be made by contacting the Privacy Officer.

How we use or disclose your personal information  
We will use and disclose personal information for the primary purpose for which it was collected. We may also use and disclose personal information for purposes related or ancillary to the main reasons we collect it, such as invoicing, reminder notices, provision of information and other services offered by us. 

Sharing information within the  Cheatshero.com  network  
Each  Cheatshero.com  entity may disclose personal information to other  Cheatshero.com  entities which will use and disclose the information only for the purpose for which it was originally collected.

Our duty of confidentiality and obligations of non-disclosure  
We have a duty to maintain the confidentiality of our clients' affairs, including personal information. Our duty of confidentiality applies except where disclosure of a client's personal information is with that client's consent, compelled by law, or for the sole purpose of avoiding the probable commission or concealment of a felony.

Gaining access to information we hold about you  
We will, on request, provide you with access to the personal information we hold about you unless there is an exception which applies under the Privacy Act such as where we have a legal duty of confidentiality or non-disclosure.

Your request to obtain access will be dealt with in a reasonable time.  Cheatshero.com  may recover from you its reasonable cost of providing you with access.

If we refuse to provide you with access to the information, we will provide you with reasons for the refusal.

Security of your personal information  
We protect any personal information that we hold from misuse and loss. We also protect it from unauthorised access, modification and disclosure.

Your personal information may be stored either in hard copy documents or as electronic data in  Cheatshero.com 's software or systems.

We maintain physical security over our paper and electronic data stores and premises, such as locks and security systems. We also maintain computer and network security; for example, we use firewalls (security measures for the Internet) and other security systems such as user identifiers and passwords to control access to our computer system.

Transfer of information to foreign countries  
We may transfer your personal information to foreign countries as part of our services. We will only transfer your personal information to foreign countries with your express or implied consent.

How to contact us  
If you wish to gain access to your personal information or make a complaint about a breach of your privacy or if you have any query on how your personal information is collected or used or any other query relating to this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [support@Cheatshero.com ](mailto:support@%C2%A0Cheatshero.com%C2%A0)
